[{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 01010110?","answerOptions":[{"answer":86,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":192},{"answer":146},{"answer":52}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 01110000?","answerOptions":[{"answer":3},{"answer":112,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":155},{"answer":183}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 10000010?","answerOptions":[{"answer":134},{"answer":158},{"answer":130,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":42}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 01101010?","answerOptions":[{"answer":182},{"answer":106,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":255},{"answer":157}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 00110101?","answerOptions":[{"answer":115},{"answer":53,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":77},{"answer":165}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 01010010?","answerOptions":[{"answer":176},{"answer":152},{"answer":82,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":108}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 00110101?","answerOptions":[{"answer":250},{"answer":80},{"answer":53,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":60}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 10010011?","answerOptions":[{"answer":85},{"answer":14},{"answer":147,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":230}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 11001010?","answerOptions":[{"answer":119},{"answer":6},{"answer":75},{"answer":202,"isCorrect":true}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 10011001?","answerOptions":[{"answer":153,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":211},{"answer":215},{"answer":118}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 11010011?","answerOptions":[{"answer":211,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":173},{"answer":252},{"answer":96}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 01000000?","answerOptions":[{"answer":64,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":93},{"answer":226},{"answer":210}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 00111111?","answerOptions":[{"answer":63,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":16},{"answer":132},{"answer":103}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 10010100?","answerOptions":[{"answer":164},{"answer":209},{"answer":148,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":7}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 00011001?","answerOptions":[{"answer":21},{"answer":221},{"answer":223},{"answer":25,"isCorrect":true}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 10001100?","answerOptions":[{"answer":68},{"answer":109},{"answer":186},{"answer":140,"isCorrect":true}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 11101111?","answerOptions":[{"answer":133},{"answer":35},{"answer":159},{"answer":239,"isCorrect":true}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 11111111?","answerOptions":[{"answer":23},{"answer":68},{"answer":255,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":114}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 11001000?","answerOptions":[{"answer":200,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":153},{"answer":69},{"answer":152}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 01000000?","answerOptions":[{"answer":64,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":235},{"answer":12},{"answer":242}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 00101100?","answerOptions":[{"answer":44,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":105},{"answer":192},{"answer":4}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 10000110?","answerOptions":[{"answer":134,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":222},{"answer":215},{"answer":100}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 11011110?","answerOptions":[{"answer":51},{"answer":222,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":179},{"answer":34}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 10101100?","answerOptions":[{"answer":247},{"answer":52},{"answer":18},{"answer":172,"isCorrect":true}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 00011101?","answerOptions":[{"answer":119},{"answer":23},{"answer":29,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":5}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 00001110?","answerOptions":[{"answer":248},{"answer":14,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":221},{"answer":249}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 11001101?","answerOptions":[{"answer":143},{"answer":140},{"answer":101},{"answer":205,"isCorrect":true}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 10100011?","answerOptions":[{"answer":187},{"answer":163,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":190},{"answer":237}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 10010101?","answerOptions":[{"answer":169},{"answer":149,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":125},{"answer":82}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 11001101?","answerOptions":[{"answer":8},{"answer":205,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":115},{"answer":241}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 01101110?","answerOptions":[{"answer":110,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":66},{"answer":65},{"answer":91}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 01010111?","answerOptions":[{"answer":87,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":63},{"answer":105},{"answer":199}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 11110010?","answerOptions":[{"answer":242,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":201},{"answer":132},{"answer":208}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 00000001?","answerOptions":[{"answer":90},{"answer":255},{"answer":182},{"answer":1,"isCorrect":true}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 00110001?","answerOptions":[{"answer":10},{"answer":49,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":152},{"answer":17}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 10011110?","answerOptions":[{"answer":186},{"answer":121},{"answer":244},{"answer":158,"isCorrect":true}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 01000110?","answerOptions":[{"answer":70,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":11},{"answer":48},{"answer":189}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 01010101?","answerOptions":[{"answer":85,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":108},{"answer":45},{"answer":205}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 00010110?","answerOptions":[{"answer":166},{"answer":22,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":206},{"answer":98}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 10001111?","answerOptions":[{"answer":105},{"answer":4},{"answer":143,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":84}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 00000001?","answerOptions":[{"answer":94},{"answer":1,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":20},{"answer":117}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 01001100?","answerOptions":[{"answer":144},{"answer":194},{"answer":77},{"answer":76,"isCorrect":true}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 10001100?","answerOptions":[{"answer":90},{"answer":108},{"answer":140,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":54}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 01000011?","answerOptions":[{"answer":234},{"answer":169},{"answer":55},{"answer":67,"isCorrect":true}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 11010010?","answerOptions":[{"answer":250},{"answer":91},{"answer":213},{"answer":210,"isCorrect":true}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 11111100?","answerOptions":[{"answer":252,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":219},{"answer":98},{"answer":135}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 00011000?","answerOptions":[{"answer":7},{"answer":201},{"answer":218},{"answer":24,"isCorrect":true}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 11100110?","answerOptions":[{"answer":92},{"answer":75},{"answer":230,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":230}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 01101111?","answerOptions":[{"answer":111,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":102},{"answer":67},{"answer":105}]},{"question":"What is the decimal equivalent of 01101100?","answerOptions":[{"answer":108,"isCorrect":true},{"answer":198},{"answer":53},{"answer":17}]}]